{
    "id": "a6386f76baaf45119b46949546295098",
    "title": "General Grammar Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The water came up ………………………………… our knees.",
            "description": "Above and over can both mean higher than.",
            "answers": [
                "above",
                "over",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "14dee4b1bb5147ae91fe157c3ac97982"
        },
        {
            "question": "They walked right …………………………….. the desert.",
            "description": "Across means on or to the other side of a flat area or surface.",
            "answers": [
                "over",
                "through",
                "across"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "c886de8565fd49809ff0da10285aa08e"
        },
        {
            "question": "She danced …………………………………. into the room.",
            "description": "We use the adverb happily to modify the verb danced.",
            "answers": [
                "happy",
                "happily",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "84f416a520f94ae4950b551b28fffbbb"
        },
        {
            "question": "I can …………………………………. recommend their service.",
            "description": "Highly is similar to very much. It shows an extreme degree.",
            "answers": [
                "high",
                "highly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f607b64db1234742a7f06a2e6b434701"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was ………………………………… punished for his crimes.",
            "description": "Justly is the adverb for the meaning ‘in accordance with justice or the law.’",
            "answers": [
                "just",
                "justly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "65b25eaf3ec74842ae18d9e8f0c1f7e7"
        },
        {
            "question": "They are ……………………………… excited about the party.",
            "description": "Pretty is similar to rather.",
            "answers": [
                "pretty",
                "prettily",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4c494a3a323142f3a030884edc613d8e"
        },
        {
            "question": "Isn’t she dressed …………………………………?",
            "description": "Prettily means in a pretty way.",
            "answers": [
                "pretty",
                "prettily",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6d002bea2c6549129705aed6e84eb9c7"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ………………………………. asleep when the thieves broke in.",
            "description": "Sound is an adverb in the expression sound asleep.",
            "answers": [
                "sound",
                "soundly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cc4d21ef18454acfa1f325cb6114d085"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was sleeping ………………………………… when the thieves broke in.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sound",
                "soundly",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b0d691c464a742f78820ba651e8d0dc5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She has eaten ……………………………………. the candies.",
            "description": "All or all of can be used before a noun with a determiner.",
            "answers": [
                "all",
                "all of",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "39cc3a1534ec452bb6842cf173dcb7df"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is not ……………………………….. successful as his wife.",
            "description": "After not, we can use as/so…….as.",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "so",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "92ead7cfa6804b0aa57a3bcc6f34842f"
        },
        {
            "question": "You need not ……………………………….. woken me up.",
            "description": "When need is used as a modal, it is followed by an infinitive without to. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "to have",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "c9b90a524d1a4091940bfeab091e0f41"
        }
    ]
}